Inventory of the Coleman Wilson Papers 1775-1989, 1919-1964
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Coleman-Wilson Papers, 1775-1989, 1919-1964.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 96 C67
1,602 items.
Letters, chiefly 1919-1964, written to Julia Gardiner Tyler Wilson (1881-1965) of Charlottesville, Virginia from Mary Haldane Begg Coleman(1875-1967) of Williamsburg, Virginia.
Mary Haldane Begg Coleman,; Julia Gardiner Tyler Wilson,; Janet C. (Janet Coleman) Kimbrough,; Alida Wilson Davison,; Woodrow Wilson.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 1,602 items, 6/19/1991.
Biographical/Historical Information
Julia Gardiner Tyler Wilson was the daughter of Lyon Gardiner Tyler and the granddaughter of President John Tyler. Mary Haldane Begg Coleman was the wife of George Preston Coleman, mayor of Williamsburg. George P. Coleman was a direct descendant of St. George Tucker.
Scope and Content Information
Letters, chiefly 1919-1964, written of Mary Haldane Begg Coleman (1875-1967) of Williamsburg, Virginia, to Julia Gardiner Tyler Wilson (1881-1965), of Charlottesville, Virginia Other correspondents include Janet Coleman Kimbrough, Mary H.B. Coleman's daughter and Alida Wilson Davidson, the daughter of Julia Gardiner Tyler Wilson.
Scrapbooks containing information on John Tyler, Tyler descendants, and the Tucker family. Photographs mainly of Coleman family and friends; collection of medals awarded to James Southall Wilson, husband of Julia Tyler Wilson. Also included in collection are a letter from Princeton University President Woodrow Wilson and two Virginia pound notes dated 1775.
Subjects covered in the collection include the Restoration of Colonial Williamsburg, the College of William and Mary, World War I and II, Begg and Tucker genealogy and life in Williamsburg, Virginia.
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is organized into 6 Series: Series 1 contains letters, Series 2 contains material relating to various material, Series 3 contains miscellaneous material, Series 4 contains photographs, Series 5 contains awards and medals, and Series 6 contains scrapbooks.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into series which are then primarily arranged chronologically by date. Those folders with multipule dates are located at the end of each series.
Index Terms
Family Names:
Begg family.; Tucker family.; Coleman family.
Persons:
Coleman, Mary Haldane Begg, 1875-1967.; Wilson, James Southall.; Wilson, Julia Gardiner Tyler, 1881-1965.; Kimbrough, Janet C. (Janet Coleman); Davison, Alida Wilson.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.
Subjects:
World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1939-1945.; College of William and Mary--History--20th century.
Geographical Names:
Williamsburg (Va.)--History--20th century.
Components List
  Series 1: Letters
- Letters, 1919-1967. (Box 1-5)
  This series is divided into yearly subseries.
  - Letters, 1919-1920., 35 items. (Box-folder 1:1-2)
    Colemans get a new Ford car, Janet Coleman attending W&M, George P. Coleman becomes highway commissioner, Wilsons move to a new house, recounting traveller's perception of Russian situation, discussion of inflation in Germany and sending German relatives money, "incendiary address to be given ... by a negro next Thursday ... " stopped by whites by getting town blacks "to let the lecturer know he was not wanted in Williamsburg ... ," Lyon G. Tyler's accident and Highway Dept. movie on Virginia, election and participation of "new voters" [women].
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, discussing the activities of the family, [August ?] 1919 - March 1920., 17 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, discussing the activities of the family, April 1920 - December 1920., 18 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, discussing the activities of the family, 1921., 25 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:3)
    Visit of a "musical aeroplane [sic]" to Williamsburg, Duke of Gloucester St. to be paved, Janet Coleman's graduation from W&M and acceptance into PBK, Janet Coleman goes to Johns Hopkins, illness and death of Annie Baker Tucker Tyler, May complains about lack of beauty of how Duke of Gloucester St. is paved.
  - Letters, 1922., 22 items. (Box-folder 1:4-5)
    George Coleman and Harry Byrd political fighting, reopening of [Marshall-Wythe] Law School, Lyon G. Tyler speaks at W&M, President's House has a fire, Janet Coleman's W&M "fraternity" Gamma Omega affiliates with Kappa Alpha Theta, Janet Coleman engaged to George Finney, Janet drops out of Johns Hopkins because of engagement, Alexander Graham Bell dies, Janet Coleman's engagement broken, Cynthia Coleman to attend Miss Ellets' [St. Catherine's] School.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, January - April 1922., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, May - December 1922., 9 items. ALsS (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, 1923., 31 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:6)
    George Coleman resigns from Highway Commission, Janet Coleman attends UVA, Wilsons to get Ford car, electricity being put in Tucker House, May and Cynthia Coleman sail to Europe, Lyon G. Tyler remarries.
  - Letters, 1924., 27 items. (Box-folder 1:7-8)
    May and Cynthia Coleman return from Europe, short discussion of Tucker family tree, building cabin at Yorktown ("Kiskiack"), discussing the London Conference, Lyon G. Tyler and wife expecting baby, fire at the Tucker House.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, February - May 1924., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, June - December 1924., 14 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Letter, 1925-1926., 43 items. (Box-folder 1:9-12)
    Description of eclipse, discussion about "teenagers," fire at W&M, Janet Coleman plans to go to Syracuse and graduates from UVA medical school, May Coleman's mother dies, Cynthia Coleman's appendix removed.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - May 1925., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, June - December 1925., 11 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - April 1926., 9 items. (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, May - December 1926., 11 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:12)
  - Letters, 1927-1928., 32 items. (Box-folder 1:13-14)
    Colemans buy a Studebaker, contrasting mourning customs of contemporary and earlier generations, Alida Wilson crowned "May Queen," discussion of Lindbergh's flight, Janet and Cynthia Coleman go abroad, [W.A.R.] Goodwin "mysteriously buying up Williamsburg," Janet Coleman marries Ray Kimbrough, Restoration buys the Coleman House.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, 1927., 20 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, 1928., 12 items. (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Letters, 1929-1930., 39 items. (Box-folder 1:15-17)
    Kimbroughs move to Norfolk, Bev[erley] Tucker's death and funeral, Mary Goodwin discovers Bodlean plate, Tucker House to be restored, Cynthia Coleman marries Singleton Moorehead, fire at Bassett Hall, Ray ["Kippy"] Kimbrough born.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of her family, 1929., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - April 1930., 12 items. (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, May - December 1930., 14 items. (Box-folder 1:17)
  - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of their families, 1931., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:18)
    Mooreheads in Boston, Alida Wilson attends Wellesley College, Colemans move back into Tucker House, sesquicentennial of Yorktown.
  - Letters, 1932., 34 items. (Box-folder 1:19-20)
    Restoration moves Confederate statue off Palace Green, Restoration begins garden of Tucker House, Lindbergh baby kidnapped, Governors meeting in Williamsburg - May mentions being "very much attracted by Franklin Roosevelt," Charles Coleman's death, Restoration of the courthouse, Nancy Wilson graduates from Sweet Briar, opening of the Raleigh Tavern, Governor's Palace being built, compilation of "Williamsburg Scrap-book," Peyton-Randolph House restored, Mary Tyler's death and funeral, "main College building" turned over to Restoration.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - August 1932., 19 items. (Box-folder 1:19)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of their families, September - December 1932., 15 items ALsS. (Box-folder 1:20)
  - Letters, 1933., 34 items. (Box-folder 1:21-22)
    Capitol and Palace being finished, mention of German friends' opinions of Hitler, thoughts on Russia and Germany.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - June 1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of their families, September - December 1933., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:22)
  - Letters, 1934., 36 items. (Box-folder 1:23-24)
    George Coleman finishes term as mayor, central heat in Tucker House, George Coleman on committee to name Restoration buildings - opposes name "Wren building," Cynthia Kimbrough born, Winston Churchill visits Williamsburg and Tucker House, Stewart Bryan becomes W&M President, Duke of Gloucester St. finished, Mooreheads move into one of Restoration houses on Duke of Gloucester St. across from the Inn.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - May 1934., 17 items. (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of their families, June - December 1934., 19 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 1:24)
  - Letters, 1935., 33 items. (Box-folder 2:1-2)
    Hostesses in Williamsburg given colonial costumes, Lyon G. Tyler illness and death, Powder Magazine and jail being restored, Kimbroughs in new home, plans for Williamsburg Inn decided.
    - Letters from May [ Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - May 1935., 15 items. (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly discussing the activities of their families, June - December 1935., 18 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Letters, 1936., 41 items. (Box-folder 2:3-5)
    May gets and dislikes her first Radio, Powder Magazine finished, description of President Roosevelt's visit to Williamsburg, furnishing of Palace and Bassett Hall for the Rockefellers.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - April 1936., 16 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, May - September 1936., 14 items. ALsS (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly about the activities of their families, October - December 1936., 11 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Letters, 1937., 36 items. (Box-folder 2:6-7)
    Andrew Mellon makes offer for Tucker House, John Randolph portrait for new National Gallery, abdication of Edward VIII, May Coleman to write about St. George Tucker, lunch with Rockefellers at Bassett Hall, Hindenburg discussed, discussion of Amelia Earhart, death of Mr. McRae of Carter's Grove, Kippy Kimbrough has appendicitis.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - June 1937., 21 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly about the activities of their families, July - December 1937., 15 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Letters, 1938., 32 items. (Box-folder 2:8-9)
    Dr [W.A.R.] Goodwin to retire from Bruton Parish, Honorary degree given to Georgia O'Keefe, George Coleman's portrait for the College of William and Mary painted, Mary Coleman transfers old Tucker letters to Colonial Williamsburg Research Office, Shirley Temple visits Williamsburg, Alida Wilson marries Charles Davison, Nancy Wilson marries Jack Drewry.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - July 1938., 17 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, August - December 1938., 15 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Letters, 1939., 25 items. (Box-folder 2:10-11)
    Mary Coleman's book, St. George Tucker, Citizen of No Mean City published, Singleton Moorehead's father's death, discussion of European situation and war, George Coleman's heart attack and recovery, Dr. W.A.R. Goodwin's death.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - July 1939., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:10)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, August - December 1939., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Letters, 1940., 31 items. (Box-folder 2:12-13)
    John D. Rockefeller's portrait painted courtesy of Williamsburg citizens, news of war from European friends, discussion of Gone With the Wind, birth of Patricia Drewry.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - August 1940., 18 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, September - December 1940., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Letters, 1941., 23 items. (Box-folder 2:14-15)
    A[ssociation for the] P[reservation of] V[irginia] A[ntiquities] sends England a motor canteen "as tribute from her first colony," establishment of the Bundles for Britain program, Williamsburg tunnel built, amazement at color photography, talk of possible invasion of England.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - August 1941., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, September - December 1941., 11 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:15)
  - Letters, 1942., 30 items. (Box-folder 2:16-17)
    Discussion of Pearl Harbor and war, Walt Disney's Fantasia discussed, George Coleman receives LL.D. and delivers the Alumni address at William and Mary, Katherine Davison born, tourist boom in Williamsburg just prior to start of gas rationing, destruction of the French fleet, One hundredth anniversary of the first Christmas tree in Virginia celebrated at the Tucker House.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - August 1942., 18 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, September - December 1942., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:17)
  - Letters, 1943., 33 items. (Box-folder 2:18-19)
    Ration books issued, General staffs of America and Britain meet in Williamsburg, Billy Goodwin missing - first Williamsburg casualty of the war, Bruce Begg (son of one of Mary Coleman's cousins) killed in Sicily.
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman]to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - June 1943., 16 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:18)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, July - December 1943., 17 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 2:19)
  - Letters, 1944., 38 items. (Box-folder 3:1-3)
    Janet Kimbrough in hospital with fluid in her lungs, Jimmy Drewry born, Robert Bryan (Stewart Bryan's nephew) killed in Italy, "Kippy" Kimbrough enrolls in Episcopal High School in Alexandria, Virginia, Colemans eat lunch with Walt Disney at the Travis House, Gen. Douglas MacArthur's return to Philippines described as "most dramatic instant in the war," Mary Coleman's vote for Roosevelt "without quite such faith in his administration, but from the conviction that no one else could do anything like so well at this juncture."
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - March 1944., 10 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, April - August 1944., 15 items. ALsS (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, September - December 1944., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Letters, 1945., 44 items. (Box-folder 3:4-7)
    Charles Davison goes to fight, German prisoners escaped from Camp Peary captured in Williamsburg, F.D. Roosevelt's death, Julia Davison dies, Robbery and fire in the Tucker House, Kimbroughs move to Richmond, war ends, Charles Davison, Jimmie and Ben Hubbard return home.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - March 1945., 10 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, April - June 1945., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, July - October 1945., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, November - December 1945., 8 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Letters, 1946., 44 items. (Box-folder 3:8-11)
    Williamsburg Inn reopens for civilians, Winston Churchill and Dwight D. Eisenhower visit Williamsburg, Cynthia Kimbrough's confirmation, Joan Hubbard born, George Coleman has mild stroke, Francis Bland Saunders living at Tucker House.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - March 1946., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, April - June 1946., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, July - September 1946., 11 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, October - December 1946., 9 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Letters, 1947., 34 items. (Box-folder 3:12-14)
    Isabel Hubbard retires from silver shop, Ray Kimbrough's mother dies, Mary Coleman goes to the movies with Abby Rockefeller, Listening to Royal Wedding on the radio [Elizabeth].
    - Letters of May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - March 1947., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, April - July 1947., 10 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, August - December 1947., 14 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Letters, 1948., 31 items. (Box-folder 3:15-16)
    Visit from President and Mrs. Truman to Williamsburg, Abby Rockefeller dies, "Kippy" Kimbrough wins a 3-year William and Mary scholarship for his chemistry examination scores, "Kippy" Kimbrough graduates from Episcopal High School, George Coleman dies, Elizabeth Coleman (George Coleman's sister) dies, "Kippy" Kimbrough enters William and Mary and joins Kappa Sigma.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - August 1948., 18 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:15)
    - Letters form May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, September - December 1948., 13 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:16)
  - Letters, 1949., 31 items. (Box-folder 3:17-19)
    George Coleman's Indian artifacts divided and given to white and "coloured" schools, Janet and Ray Kimbrough separate, "Kippy" Kimbrough gets polio.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - April 1949., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:17)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, May - September 1949., 12 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:18)
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman], wife of George P. Coleman, to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, wife of James Southall Wilson, mainly concerning the activities of their families, October - December 1949., 7 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:19)
  - Letters, 1950., 27 items. (Box-folder 3:20-21)
    Gallery of Phi Beta Kappa Hall [now Ewell Hall] collapses, fire at one of the taverns leaves one man dead and several badly hurt, Jimmie Hubbard ordered to report to camp in Georgia, "Kippy" Kimbrough visits Bermuda to help recover from polio, "Kippy" Kimbrough returns to William and Mary, Robert Tucker of Baltimore dies at age 102, Jane Kimbrough gets a job at Camp Lee, Restoration gets two buses "to transport tourists or ticket holders about town...," Mary Coleman finds, reads, and burns letters she wrote to George.
    - Letters from May [Mary Haldane Begg Coleman] to Julia [Tyler] Wilson, January - July 1950., 15 items. ALsS. (Box-folder 3:20)